thecoli.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy | Sports, Hip Hop & Piff - The Coli

  * 

## Privacy Policy

Effective May 27, 2018. Last Revised May 27, 2018

This privacy policy sets out how The Coli uses and protects any information that you provide, whilst using The Coli products and services. This includes, but is not limited to, TheColi.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

The Coli is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information provided by you to The Coli , by which you can be identified, will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

The Coli may change this policy as and when necessary. It is your responsibility to check this privacy policy periodically to ensure you agree with any changes.

## What information we collect

When using any products and services provided by The Coli, we _may_ require some or all of the following information:

  * name
  * address
  * telephone number
  * email address
  * information related to any financial transactions which may be carried out

Additionally, whilst using the TheColi.com website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected:

Internet Protocol (IP) address 

  * geographical location
  * browser type and version
  * operating system
  * referral source
  * length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity

## What we do with the information we collect

The information you provide to The Coli is required for, but not limited to, the following reasons:

  * internal record keeping
  * access to the TheColi.com website, associated websites and sub-domains
  * account management
  * account confirmation and account reset

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to The Coli is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

## How we use cookies and IP addresses

TheColi.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, use small text files, called cookies, to store information in your web browser. The information stored may include preferences, session identification, HTTP information, and IP address. Our full Cookie Usage is detailed on a separate page. [Click Here for our Cookie Policy](http://www.thecoli.com/help/cookies%22)

You can set your browser to not receive cookies, but this may limit your ability to use TheColi.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

IP addresses of computers used to visit XenForo.com and any associated websites and sub-domains are stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question.

Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time.

## Links to other websites

TheColi.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with The Coli.

The Coli has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and The Coli cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites.

## Controlling your personal information

When using the TheColi.com forum, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account.

The Coli will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you security information, product updates, or other information pertaining to The Coli , or your account.

If you discover any of the information The Coli holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made.

## Rights

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please contact us. If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may contact us to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please contact us if you would like us to remove your personal data.

## Acceptance of this policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

## Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.
